my socksoft and hesitant footsteps are deliberate and with each planting a new vista of the city is desaturating, leaning on Nadia crushing a bloody nit between her nails in the dark end of the hallway alone , in tedium the folks are sucking smooth stones, whispering in the narrow stairs -- «The „Geezer“» Still is In Ownership Of This Place You Know, You Just Stop Paying Rent, He Isn't Going To Get a Court Order, How Could He, Just Don't Move Out -- the downcast queues are full of either victims of resettlement or punitive exiles folding jejunoform back on their static stringloops--the mass swaying in place with varying thicknesses of paperwork accruals--staring through each other they are staring through the asphalt and concrete at a variety of negative altitudes in orientations of all degress besides the downstream of the stationary queue, dry and cracking sneaker soles are sloughing off thin layers on the increasingly fresh and abrasive concrete toward the great cube of the «Municipal Center», each footstep through the balls of my feet is agony that in my conscious registration is joyous at feeling connection to the asphalt running unbroken in pooling warmth to the shadowing awning of home, I am awaiting the ultimate collapse because I fear pulling it all down onto me, Cherdyn is a decrepit wilderness of glass with the appearingly decadant reexposure of walls and landscape from the melancholy retreating floodwaters of the fetid tepid river, I am sitting against a standpipe motionless ferrying discomfort into dissipation through the distribution of my blood, all the windows capturing flat reflections of the sky are bearing the red triangle decal only one is missing half and this window is very high, lilacs in eruption and sickly thick fragrance in abundance, the countenance and glazegazing of the shuffling and searching exiles--distant eyes on a vector chording through the globe toward home--, my shoes are missing from the personal property area of «Patient Discharging» in a plastic tub where just my shirt in twain and my distraught jacket that I am trading for the hospital tunic in the middle of the lobby standing halfnude and dressing to the accompaniment of the shiftcommand gifting me with the tractionsole anklesocks and hustling us through the outer door in avoidance of the gawking queue of all other dischargees demanding complimentary ownership of their anklesocks, the cubic building in polymer stuccorendering festooning and bunting and medallions, an enormous trompeloeil keystone in tearose atop two faux taupe granite tetrahedonal acones, the parameters of my exile with the requirement of visiting the municipal «Commandant» on regular and frequent intervals, we are munching some dandelion greens from a collection Nadia is amassing in your dresspocket, the foamy cube is great and ambiguous with seeming entasis on its edges insisting the ornament gagging facade forward over us within its shade, flat black windows in the concealment of patterning and ornament are stacking dozens of storeys, cladwood siding--particles of planer shavings and wastewood and newsprint in bondage of wax and resin with fibrous jacketing--prone to disintegration with exposure to moisture, on a tackboard within a nichesurround of styrofoam moulding the waitlist for one of the few «massives» in Cherdyn--covetously in the construction of an overly spacious grid including the «Municipal Center»--is ponderous and generally a distant residential possibility for those not in direct service to the ADA or its semipublic entities, the entry foyer of the «Municipal Center» is conversely a tiny deadend navel full of lint and a relentless applique of lozenges and heptagrams of various rouges across walls and ceiling and floor, we are waiting, we are not alone, the heatwave in the airless room is austere is oppressive, delerium, in the mustardy geometric applique is material joinery in nonconformance with the patterning, a panel is opening into the foyer under its own propulsion and Nadia is taking my hand through the passage, I am taking Nadia's hand wandering empty hallway boulevards with metal doors, in the tedium of waiting in the queue stallingly loping Nadia is leafing through the waitlist out of fatalistic curiosity about our location in the roster and is returning with dejection -- We are Not On The List At All -- Nadia's agreement with «the „Geezer“» is for residency in the kitchen--the only remaining vacant plat of the house--every building with domestic designation is completely public and as such the dwelling superscriptions are specific down to the geographic corner of rooms and rooms have numbers in sequence through each building either in the order they are accessible after the front door or beginning in a circular motion to the left and spiralling inward--although the only space that is not obstructive to the function of the room is beneath an austere and filthy kitchen table standing in the center of the room, our location in Cherdyn is by the following definition--in all ADA filings and documentation about my exile--10-122 Prospect 03.X where «ex» is the designation of a room's center, the sage green house across from the vacant plat serving as a waystation for the migration of certain dark and regal butterflies, only one folkle is queuing into the foyer is pulling shut the black glass door, a long corridor with no doors is leading to an elevator without callbuttons or floor selectors is opening with our proximity, blackdots of people flitting at the far ends of corridors, transoms over the metal doors are mruky with texture of pyramids capturing inner dark and hallway glaring, blackdots crossing through intersections, a distant transom is dark is luminous, the rectangular judas is ajar allowing crisply cold exsufflation, the «Commandant» in a drab greatcoat swallowing any chair he is sitting upon behind a barren and very large--an obstruction of the entire width of the room--metal desk in a small room with six doors, almost grinning reading my face my fear, -- stay Behind The Gray Line, This is Not A Conversation, You are To Report Here To Me And Only To Me Remember My Face On Every Third Day Bring All Documentation And The Presence Of Your Wife is Not A Requirement -- without reviewing our paperwork or my documentation, breezy seeds are clinging to my anklesocks resting on a low spallingly ruinous concrete wall in relative shade and Nadia is uprooting a thicket of nettles at her feet for the growing redeemable sheaf collection in her totebag, slowmixing vapor is sheeting from the gap under one of the doors behind the desk, almost a distraction from the onerousness of the «Commandant's» terms the delicious coolness is precipitating on my hands and the hydrological cycling of my chest hair from the slashfray rift of my hangning open shirt, the hillock of Nadia's chin is glistening beneath an almost relief grin, the lefthand door on our side of the desk is swinging inward on mysterious silent and prompt propulsion, with burgeoning understanding of the geography from many orientations the peeking above the skyline Cherdyn «Municipal Center» of the ADA--ADAemone colloquially, those of us living and living and living are wondering which is worse between endless deferral in the byzantine bureaucratic ADA hierarchy or unyielding abstraction in the intellectual cult of the Daemonic congress, though how different are hanging and decapitation--is relatively near the hospital, the distances from the top floor I am singling out my hospital room window with the red triangle half missing, we are waiting for assistance with the pumpcar dormant against its stopblocks even further up the valley than the «Municipal Center», dry blood on my hangingopen shirt, we are waiting in the wire bench of the pumpcar for an able second on the walkingbeam, two soaking through shirts wrenching from their waistbands with envious industry, all of the baggage is resting in my lap, Nadia deftly maneuvering the joystick through the fluid lace of omnidirectional tracks with only the most instinctual geographic sensibility, the breeze of movement of consciousness and living with this strange city in passage closing my eyes to the breeze rifling in my billowing open the ruinous dressshirt I am everywhere, unreasonable unendurable exhaustion, people living everywhere for various reasons, the rhythmic action of the walkingbeam and the two men in silence, brighter skylight is whiting out through higher tree spires where the viol the violet and the vine entwining the verve of valleys and towers and domes of dull dirt and loose rocks are slipping and tumbling clicking over one another in our stumbling up to the frenzying of carrion birds, clouds clouds and clouds, the lessee payment for the negative space under the kitchen table is 1,84ƫ--payable to the municipal authorities of Cherdyn--of which «the „Geezer“» is collecting less than 0,36ƫ if anything, fantasies of the stillness of the apartment click engagement rotation leverpump resting click engagement creaking rotation leverpump bloodrush silence click engagement thin whispy hair blowing resting bright white leverpump coasting through cool air freewheeling click engagement--over asphalt swath traversing derelict sidewalks buildings far from each other and flat in affect into the invariably winding foothill avenues on the valley walls spotty with dodgy dingy residences, the house is tenuous in its hermeticism and differential pressures are draughty sucking in hot air and sequestering it with foul breath and the effluvia wall cavities, the sundry vulturepickings of Anna's feet on my tongue, overcoats and trenchcoats and jackets limp on pegs beside the front door, mold spores on the air clinging to bulbous mist beadlets implanting in wall cavities and impregnating lowquality sheetrock of such porosity blooming with blackness neath painting and painting and painting, «the „Geezer“»--who, with the adoption of a famous Daemone cartoonist's name, is creasing and glazing within the leaden weight of perpetual misery--through bare and windowpane raindusty and dustdrifting divisions of false applique muntins is staring at an angle of one eye upon the wall and one oblique out the window without reaction to our approaching up the spalling and nettlesome concrete path through damp and soilfudge, the smoothest stones, upon a placid island of ignorance, in rapturous exhaustion Nadia and I lying together hard on the bare linoleum, no configuration of my body is bearable on the floor in thick sleep arriving upon concentricwaves of pain from my shoulder is darkening the persistent coldness of the overhead light with pulsations pricklingly visible and in the fine nerves along my hairline spreading a torpid blanket, there is no thread matching the stitchery in my ruinous shirt, in the front room are the pallets of a group of 3 working age youths--«Arest the „Hairy“» and «Arest the „Merkin“» and «Naderi of the „Caves“» cooperating on making rent though disdainful of one another and each is claiming residence in a different corner--in the fourth corner is the front door--, in the sitting room are the belongings of a young couple «Astein» and «Strea» whose baby is inside the closet where «Strea's» sister is feeding her behind the obstruction of their aloof drooling borzoi «D» sleeping against the door in the absence of the parents, in the formal living room the heads of twin sisters--«actresses» of scant reputation--are chatting in the bay window on the outside wall mending theatrical knickers and bloomers behind crates forming a low partition across from two silent and invisible families behind sheets are hanging hypotenusal from the wall in the opposite corners, through into the kitchen Nadia and I are sitting under the kitchen table my neck cranking down further exacerbating the limited mobility of my shoulder, the onion musk of «the „Geezer“» finely folding into the absorbent coils of his linty aerophanous skin and with the propellant of his lurching through the kitchen is fractosmic upon the otherwise stagnant air where it is lingering with appreciable viscosity falling in gentle eddies to rest in a noxious cushion across our linofloor of slumber, «Setian» a slippery ADA mollusk within the spider infestation of the attic at the top of the stairs--a very large and wooden triangular prismatic chamber with no finishings over stud cavities of froth and egg sac delicacies--, letting onto a narrow hallway with a bare stovepipe running through it, the sole bathroom with the blessing of a single bare lightbulb, the front bedroom where «the „Geezer“» is staring at the door of a closet where--they are whispering on the back stoop--a widow with the name «A» has a residence, and the rear bedroom--an awkwardly long space with a dormer and a sloping attic ceiling--containing a childless couple wearing earplugs while reading and another old man sleeping in the dormer and in the corner the belongings of an industrious young student «Neidar» whose elderly parents are playing a cardgame on a crate between their pallets in the closet, «the „Geezer“» muttering about the toppling in on itself of the house, for the widening of every joint, in the bitter and humid cold ice shims are prying -- This is My Grave, My Grave, My Grave -- the house is collapsing in a pouf of sawdust and mold with everyone still inside with him sitting in his chair watching the perspective shift, the sweetness of slowly decaying nettle fasces, spiralling in my ear delicate and deadly dull though resonant clickings of smooth fistsize stones falling across one another, «the „Geezer“» is leaning face down between his arms reaching to the flyrails of an extension ladder leaning against the outside wall of the house where powder is raining down crumblingly into his dead silver hair, mruky vapor simmering off of the riverflow is lending a light convection to the street air less oppressively and stagnant than the still stifling house and the shuffling of boots across the kitchen linoleum out into the avenues and adhoc circuit of the neighborhood and into the unbuildable areas rising up the valley walls for walking and looking in the trunkdrifts of pineneedles or tumbledown cairns of discrete stray landslides for an outstretching hand or feathering forth of Anna's fine bangs, molars and the clicking of bones, «the „Geezer“» is cornering the young student in the kitchen doorway -- «Neidar» You are Studying Psychology are You Not -- · -- No Sir I am Studying Industrial and Organizational Psychology -- · -- Right, Yes Then Certainly This Knowledge is Easily Accessible, What Is The Proper Terminology For A Woman--Or Just A Person Rather--Who Has A Commitment To Pushing The Buttons Of Those Around Them, Or Just Some Of Those Very Near To Them -- · -- Truly Sir, I Don't Have That Knowledge -- the lad is looking down at Nadia below the table -- It is Madness Though Is It Not -- · --  Yes, Certainly -- · -- It's Dyscrasia -- · -- No Sir That Isn't Sounding Correct, Schizotypal is Something -- · -- Yes -- · -- Do They Have Belief In Magic -- «the „Geezer“» is casting his eyes downward startlingly finding Nadia and myself feigning slumber -- I am Not Certain -- · --  I Really am More Knowledgeable About Hierarchical Labour Phalanxing -- · -- She is Bilious -- exchanging the collection of enough nettles in a totebag for a secondhand pair of shoes, we are both looking in dejection at the feltboots on the counter, I am imploring the storekeeper for a pair of topboots even in my logic is the awareness of the ridiculousness of such an exchange, hardly 2 kg of nettles are gingerly burdening the scale, even with the notorious tares of municipal vendors our offerance isn't remotely commensurate with a pair of leather topboots, the kitchen cabinets empty of comestibles are housing only the remote accessories of eating--not plates and cups, or forks and spoons, but a garlicpress, a pastrycutter, a potatoricer, small funnels, spatulas, peelers, pitters, trivets, nothing beneficial to the consumption of a single ingredient raw meal, much less a hot meal of any complication--as well as all of the general storage for the roominghouse occupants replacing the closets housing cousins or grandparents or inlaws of families that are residing in rooms with closets, the kitchen cabinets are too small for rental, we are not alone, «Setian» is arguing with «Naderi „of the Caves“» on the benevolence of systematic bureaucratic oppression -- You are Obedient To Blind Impulses, Which In Itself is A Form Of Slavery, We In Submission To The Meticulous And Orderly ADA Providence are More Free Than The Dolt Who is A Slave To Systems Of Which They are Ignorant -- taking his hand in speaking in puffing into the youth thrustingly they are in the clutter of his dwelling corner, the froth of spiderwebbing clinging in extension to his frizzle of hair, Nadia is slowly examining and the contents of «Strea's» sewing kit--a loose assortment of ornate fasteners, notions that she is handling each one after the other and turning over in her hand--in a small plush crate with quilting of fabric marbleization is lifting out a tailorstape a tomato pincushion lifting out a small manillaenvelope of buttons holding each in her hand with prolongment of fascination and novelty is tucking a long needle into the collar of my dressshirt tatteringly across her lap, in every accidental cairn is effulgent pale dolphin skin in the cavern crimpsheets of voidspace emanating light of its own through the stone tessellation of space, Nadia is rolling over and pinning under a seamallowance along the scissor diagonal through the shirtfront for a crisp joint and tighter fit with the consumption of more fabric awkwardly going against the axis of my body, feeling hands curling convexly into the stone cupping at the terminal point of the cave, in the swaddling tender needling of my hairline in the parallelity of slowly the needletip is emerging through the placket into Nadia's left fingertips rolling the sensation of the slender wire in her whorls mending my shirt in our cubby, a rectangular prism in concrete with inversion of its vertical edges and railings along its top edges with strange brackets chamferingly at the vertices, taut double thread is caressing its own length against the coming together puckering shirt fabric, the autoparks the roofless boxes the negligent lawns the baking rhizomes the shady shadows are nearly forests and sylvan in all of their features--leaflitter, loam, umbrage and gentle moss of windfall and the scattering of trunkpulp--while splitting the asphalt and strange intraswath subductions and uplifting slopes of tumbledown asphalt eruptions of granules and greater stones and rocks, on the walking portion of the interminable trek to the «Municipal Center» I am searching among the rocks, clambering up a dewy nettleslope toward a deceptively happenstance cairn against a windfall logdam, weedtree bosks in laciness of omnidirectional pumpcar track, at a stopblock in the forest the queue for a pumpcar is very long in the wavering umbrage, in leaflitter in umbrage I am resting my palm atop the ashplant my free hand in the slashpocket of my thin jacket beside a rubble almost wall with the persistently warm steelmuzzle on the downy hammock of skin from inion to cervical vertebra capital, the rhythm of all Cherdyn appointments with the commandant is cycling together, folks are sitting on small collapsible tripods with binders and columns of paper on their laps, partners are collecting nettles or the odd mushroom and children are playing among the rocks arranging their pale figures against the black pavement doodling in idleness, Nadia is holding our place in line with the totebag full of my documentation, with difficulty climbing an asphaltic hillock and down into a dale funneling dew into a ravine to a silent oilsheen creeklet is fluming along a long smooth ash limb suitable for a walkingstick or wand for surveyal, dry black flecks of blood are shaking loose from Nadia's short hair, rubber weedtree trunks are bending but not breaking, my pride and adoration are tingling with Nadia's confidence her deft fingers are guiding us through the forest with the joystick, our small nameless group is walking, waiting on the second leg of pumpcar transit, through the streets with the few folks from our pumpcar chewing nettles we are all encountering the tail of a queue deep out into the town, the tearose cornice of the «Municipal Center» stucco is visible over the facade across the road from our queue, leaving my ashplant beside a group of six wary men with bowls of water at their feet are leaning into the gritty scratchcoat of a crumbling masonry wall leaning threateningly over them, we are shuffling across a road running away on axis with the foyer of the «Municipal Center» beyond strata of downstream queueings filing past dormant autos across the road, two doors are opening in the foyer, -- Remain Standing -- faux marquetry flakingly spalling on the floor and territories so barren are revealing the joints of hidden doors, the «Commandant» is sitting at a desk with a thin sheaf of loose papers breathing at the far corner with the slight draughtiness of the far doors--fewer in number than my recollection but more than necessary--, he is looking only at Nadia is gazing her knees where one hand is lacing over mine--the other hand further from me is scratching her scalp absently--, -- Come Back Tomorrow -- difficulty ignorning that Nadia's name is prevalent on the top sheet of paper, melodious humming in sonic quantification of reactionary movement on the space between movements of air through the city, we are rolling dandelion leaves around dandelion stems dripping with mustard from small pouches, breathy racing away siren sounding over the whole of the valley from one direction then another although not moving sources only the breezes are gently fluctuating--manifolds of tree canopies are actuating--a man and women in thin overcoats are carrying large smooth stones, bitterness of the largest fronds and grit in the teeth, stones are clicking together dead clanging, a pod of pensioners with stones are napping under the canopies of a Daemonic natural preservation, the asphalt is in plates adrift on dusty soil radiating from a concrete basin full of windfall, the clicking of river water, the perfect shape and proportion of stone is perfectly crosssectional with the void under the neck for assistance with sidesleeping, speaking as they are drifting into simmering sleep -- I am Afraid You Must be Saying Goodbye To Tobacco -- · -- I am Quite Done For, The Only Luxury I am Leaving Of My Former Magnificence is Tobacco, With Money I am Smoking A Quarter Unit A Day -- · -- You Must Additionally be Saying Goodbye To Vodka -- · -- You are Knowing Of Course, Sir, I am Drinking Four Liters On A Good Afternoon -- · -- I am Having Suspicions You are In The Spirit World Yourself -- · -- I am Not Quite Summoning A Recollection, My Belief is Yes, I am Not Remembering A Thing, Only «whispering» A Daemon Giving A Speech As We Are Lying There Dying Of Alcohol's Merciful Suffocation, He is Weeping, That Scoundrel, The Corruptible Receiver, Exhaling A Smokescreen -- · -- Your Mother, She Is -- · -- No, Please Don't, I am Living The Life Of An Angel -- as they are drifting into simmering sleep, Nadia--a secret consciousness independent from me--is asking about for a sheet or towel, a thin layer of gentle warmth across the asphalt soft and pliable is folding over the slumberers and their totebags are tumbling over spilling more stones and nettles and a crusty sausage half, melodious humming is arising in the silence between tree canopies rattling, the dampness of Anna's skin glowing in the rocks is the desperate crouching of my creaking knees and leaning on my able arm sliding three fingers into the laminose emptiness toward the coolness and the luminance underneath the topmost stone my pointerfinger is prying up the discovery of a nest of translucent firefly larvae indulging their aestival appetites, «the „Geezer“» on his hands and knees along the concrete watertable is collecting fragments of the flaking false wood siding into a paint tray, we are not alone, I am tacking half of a bedsheet to the side of the table facing the cabinets restricting our exposure to the looming roominghouse dwellers--fending off the fleas and lice--, although we all in the house are in various ways ostracizees the designation by no means is a certainty that some one of them are not nonchalantly accruing as much information about their fellows as possible for parlayance into some further «in» as an informant or a commutation or even an ADA appointment of minimal yet desirable importance, the knowledge that I am an intellectual, that my interests are even passing upon books our critical thought--much less my name upon a dossier of my columns or the secrecy of my poem objects in the surrogate retention of Nadia's consciousness only for consumption by the ear--is causation for everyone in the house is gratuitously waiting for some morsel from me that is their chit out of this purgation, «Arest „the Hairy“» eating fermentuous leek paste from a spatula and scanning the shade below the table at asleep Nadia's ankles beneath the rolldown of her short stockings, lime and aromatic mildew at the end of the dormant cave crawling bellydown in damp one way forward no way back with an entire queue is pulling at the shoes in front of them into the tapering throat into the pencilpoint with outstretching hands into the terminus of the passage those in the rear or depths of the queue upstream of the narrow flattener are chimneying out of the entrapment although those in the restrains of the terminus are awaiting starvation or collapsing--either for crushing or for extension of the passage--, hot sweat sheen in the breeze is not comforting is not cooling, there is no thread matching the stitchery of my jacket, «the „Geezer“» muttering about his longing to simply be a tenant in his own home, black specks on the walls are snapping into place and disappearing, black specks are appearing all over the walls, interminably «Setian» pulling the gouts of tissuey spiderweb from his beard and the damp hairs from his occipital, for the ADA to purchase or even mercifully commandeer the house so that «the „Geezer“» may never leave his chair--maintenance is continually necessary but the fantasy of ADA oversight is delegating all upkeep to their notoriously mercurial facilities corps--, why would the ADA take notice, how would their soft focus clarify on this home even as one of the few remaining public homes in Cherdyn, interment in the ossuary of negative space, it seemed outlandish that they might subsume such a ruinous heap, shelving on standards everywhere laden with accumulation, possibly because they knew it would benefit him, benefit someone, as much as it could have the potential to make other suffer deeper torments and indignities, the gravemarker is another corpse whose gravemarker is another human corpse, whiteheat and heatmist baking the air are baking the thin roof shingles and attic of absent insulation convecting the hot dryrot and volatile effluvia through failures in shoddy construction, we are not alone in the woods, applying a bituminous poultice to the flaking and splitting areas of planks on the wall with his fingertip and pressing a chips of the material from a spallspoil collection in a shallow painttray into the moist sealant, ashplant through the grass is clicking, my breath is halting with every softness at the tip of the ashplant, «Strea's» plush purple paisley and turquoise wicker sewing kit is beside the table leg inside the portion of our dwelling behind the sheet where Nadia--my thin jacket and its loosely attendant arm are lying in her lap--is absently sorting through its contents for a bobbin or card of thread complimentary to the fabric, she is loosening the free end of an orange thread--and purple and black and grey and beige and red regardless of applicable color theories--and is methodically laying it over the iceblue fabric gauging the diminishment or enhancement of its impact as a slender inscription, delicate embodiment of the river, Nadia with the selection of scarlet thread and doubling it through the needle, «the „Geezer“» muttering about the widow «A» -- This Woman is The Death Of Me, Not In Torment But In Negligence And Silence, Somebody Please Talk To Me, I Can't Escape Her Silence, She has Everyone Silent With Radiation From That Authoritative Contemptuous Paralytic Closet -- shuffling into the room to repair something or clean something, he is sitting in a chair in the window, I am feeling smart and alert in my jacket, my summary execution is astride Anna's cairn over a shallow excision of rectangular earth, he is climbing a ladder up the outside of the house to wrench leaves from the mouth downspout is liberating fetid tea out across the splashblock and slowing silty in a translucent sienna reservoir on the concrete, the action of the pumpcar, strong bodies and wide shoulders a man and a woman are pumping the walkingbeam, my eyes and the evaporative cooling of the breeze weaving a path occupying all possibilities of sad Cherdyn in a fine fabric shutting my eyes into all places with the mutable breeze deflecting off of the concrete «massives» faintly edgewise with cabbage is soaking in tart mustard beside the sad little bookshelf in the apartment, a childish bookshelf, relentless applique of lozenges and heptagrams of various rouges across walls and ceiling and floor, dust, we are waiting, we are not alone, the heatwave in the airless room is austere is oppressive, delerium, in the mustardy geometric applique a panel is opening into the foyer under its own propulsion I am walking alone through the passage to a waiting ajar elevator door closing behind me hydraulically groaning beneath the cab the pressure of air pushing from above to below is seeping through the eggcrate ceiling, a pegboard of disparate cups with handles is quaking and clinking at «Arest the „Hairy“» and «Arest the „Merkin“» and «Naderi of the „Caves“» all passing through to the back door, scarification on eggshell paint surfaces where listening devices are hiding in thin walls, the empty corridors of the «Municipal Center» are dark and silent with filtration of soft skylight--auroral--through the pyramidal glass texture is wafting pale with hallucinatory peach, each arrangement of stones--badges, tetractys of the decad, runic rough breathing, cantabrian, certifications, heraldry, consumptive blazons, crossings and elder signatures, all manners of complex and hermetic veves, diacritical pebbles, graphemes, logical connectives--contradictory or tautological or implicatory or negatory--lozenges, existential quantifications, branching vectors, nazars, magic circles of stones are forming enclosures around bosks of weedtrees, checkerboards, penatcles, rosicrucian geometries, «„Landolt“ Cees», circles of stones around cobblings of small empty vessels, infantile optotypes--apples or singlefamily homes or windows or circles--long meticulous pairs of parallel lines, the triangles of earth and air and water and fire, the anthropomorphic pyramid of sulfur, the cat penis of sulfur, personal cosmograms, the spermatozoan digestion of «Leo», the mutual oral stimulation of cancerous dissolution, the upright cairn of globus cruciger--is an encryption of discreet loneliness, a faraway door is ajar with daylight suspension into the dark corridor seemingly pulsating with my approaching footsteps, the queue is halting and stuttering, the windowless room is empty and dim with the luminance at the sill of a door behind the desk and murmuring through the steel, the declaration of a sign on the desk «THE „COMMANDANT“ IS OUT», spitting out witherings of nettle stems for placing her bones in my mouth, I am sitting alone in the possible daylight glowing swelling in the room, the riverbank is a concrete surface visibly beneath the crepe surface, cairns of mossy stones near the water promising tolerable stools in a tableau otherwise recondite in ghoulish desertion by obscurant ruinous warehouses and small dockcranes, the insufferable pungency of fishy floaters, intuitional stone markings by the quarry of the velvet afternoon of adolescent ennui, a man is collecting the corpses of riverine fauna with a long bident, it is beside the river a melody unfurling without sound in the codification of persistent savourings of decay are drawing my ashplant to the the relics of Anna's granoblastic bones nonfoliate among the rocks, sorting through the rocks for those calciferous relicts responsible for the humming and pocketing them in particular for sucking stones, a tiny bone from Anna's foot on my tongue is tumbling against my teeth widening I am rolling the bespoke surfaces against the inside of my lips and wet flesh of my cheeks, the warmth and oppression of the still house is a block filling the front room of the house, on Nadia's countenance is distance--visions of boarding a transport outside the «Municipal Center» staring stolid through the curvature of the globe abandoning me in Cherdyn easily and without repercussions--returning to the kitchen with the thickening dossier and a red ear, dampness and hives flushing on my skin along my spine and beneath my ribs through my shirt and threatening sweatsalt bunting across my jacket I am peeling off but in lifting my stiff arms I am reaching a paralytic altitude insufficient for hanging the jacket on one of the pegs I am folding it over my forearm, -- I Don't Know, What Do You Want To Do -- I am decrepit and adrift, uncertain about the «Commandant's» expectations for my attendance and the rhythm of visitations ascramble, emptymouthingly Nadia is playing with me at «Interrogations» beneath the table, -- Would You Like Some Vodka Brother -- · -- My Stomach is Saying I Shouldn't But Thankfully I am Familiar With The Feeling -- · -- Your Stomach is Upset, are We Upsetting You Brother -- · -- No, No It is The Vodka -- · -- You are Drinking A Great Deal Of Vodka -- · -- Water Please -- · -- As You are Writing This Article are You Targeting Any Other Member Of The Committee On Accounts Besides «Treas» -- · -- No -- · -- Why Him, Why This Servant Of The Daemone, A Contributor, Fostering The Wellbeing Of The Folks, do You Not Care About Your Fellows -- · -- I am Not Choosing Him, He is The One, I am Thinking The Idea Of Fealty is Making Us Desperate, Seeing Ourselves Animalistic and Hideous, Needing A Benevolent Parent, Making Us Acknowledge The Fact We Are Dependent And Eating Us Gradually -- · -- What are You Doing, Josef -- · -- I'm Uncertain -- · -- Avoiding Conversational Interplay is Especially Important With The Daemone, It is Softening You, But You are Adding What is Relevant, Yes Or No, Anything Beyond That is Dangerous, You are Not Softening, You are Not Flowing, They are Lying To You, The Daemone are Liars, They are Lying For Confusion, But They are Also Mixing Untruths With The Truth In Prying You Away From Yourself, Attacking You Psychologically, So Don't Listen, Remember, Do Not Listen, Only Hear -- · -- Yes, Of Course -- · -- Just Yes -- · -- Yes -- · -- So That I am Gaining A Better Understanding, You Are Writing This Article And Submitting It Straight To The «the „Editor“» -- · -- Yes and They are Seeming Happy With It -- · -- Just Yes -- · -- Yes -- · -- They are Happy Because You are Delivering A Public Servant Up For Ridicule -- · -- You are Baiting Me, Do You Not Think I am Knowledgeable About This -- · -- I Do, You are -- · -- I am Not In Prison -- · -- No You are Not -- Nadia is looking at a greasy smudging on the leg of the table, -- It is Possible To Build A Case Against Any Man, You Needn't be Guilty Of Anything, The Suspect is Easily Finding Their Way Into Entanglement In The Web Of Ingenuius Constructions The ADA is Jeweling Around Every Utterance, They Simply are Keeping Him On The Line -- · -- So -- · -- So You are Silent -- and I am silent in the audibleness of conversations occurring throughout the house in tiers of volume, «the Commandant» is not in possession of the proper paperwork, trekking through gauzy glare and sunburn by pumpcar, -- is «the „Editor“» Calling You -- · -- Nobody is Calling Me, I am Not Hearing From Anyone Only A Veritable Autobus Full Of Feedback -- · -- From Whom -- I am Not Recognizing Any Of The Names, I am Suspicious Of Guidance, I am Striving For Internal Congruency Only, Wholeness, I am Not Oppositional To Defending My Decisions, But Not Simply Because Someone is Needing Bureaucratic Fulfillment, I am Not Desirous Of Rote Interaction -- · -- So You are Writing This Article For The Satisfaction Of Your Own Personal Vendetta -- · -- Nadia -- · -- What About The Poem -- · -- Nadia -- · -- You Are Finding Enjoyment In The Audience are You Not -- · -- No -- What Awareness are You Bringing With Your Labors -- & -- Absolutely None, I am Only Desirous Of Working -- · -- There is Documentation of You Describing Your Poems As Critical To Your Journalistic Efforts -- · -- It's important, Yet I Most Folks are Reading Only The Articles and That is Quite Fine -- · -- So The Articles are Completely Separate -- · -- I am Not Saying That, I am Saying It Is Fine If Folks are Only Reading The Articles -- · -- How Are You Placing Yourself In The Mindset Of One Practice Or The Other -- · -- I am knowledgeable About The World, My Rearing is In This Thinking, I am Confident Even If The Landscape Is Slightly Different, Sensibility is Recursive, Urges and Proclivities are Resurfacing -- Nadia is sucking stones I am sucking bones against my teeth, mizu, annaffiare, clicking the transcription of Annagrams, Tetragrammaton of her swimming, aqua, vody -- are You Reading Over Your Own Works With Any Rigorous Repetition -- · -- No -- · -- Why Not -- · -- This is, Knowing This, I am Not Responsive -- · -- What Other Journalists are You Reading -- · -- I am Not Reading Anyone -- · -- Because You are Busy -- · -- I am Not Responsive -- · -- Poems -- · -- I am Not Reading Anyone -- · -- You are Losing Ground Then -- · -- I Don't Really, I am Not Really Considerate Of The Culture, I Have A Preference For My Own Things, Believe It Or Not My Journalistic Prose Is The Most Spiritually Combative -- · -- Elaboration On That -- · -- No -- incessant whisperingly hidden implicit bargains protract freedom, taking the seam between her thumb and pointerfinger and kneadingly across its length rubbing the velvet oiliness of her whorls into the thread Nadia is unifying her remediation of the jacketsleeve with the tension of its injury, Nadia is confirming our dwelling superscription with «Strea» in the kitchen--our conversation simplistic in the embodiment of prerequisite reflectivity between two strangers or even very close acquaintances which we are not--with «D» lolling beneath the table is reproducing Nadia's sleeping posture and her warmth and the woolen moisture of her respiration, Nadia is tucking a letter in a long envelope into her thin trenchsweater, I am feigning slumber squinting at her ankles receding, haze is condensing on my high hairline, oscillations of honor and shame over my fortune of private interment in the acrid aroma of tannery leather and brainmatter I am tasting blood in the eruption of sinuses funneling dark pulpiness into soft gravesoil against my gasping tongue, «Naderi „of the Caves“» and «the „Arests“» are coming in the back door rollicking leaflitter shaking loose from their bootsoles toward the creaking of stairs audible only to Nadia and myself with our ears pressing the lineoleum membrane pantomiming sleep--an exceptionally useful talent second only to unbreaking silence--across the joists and woodframing bootsoles descending the stairs toward the young men winding their way through the clutter and hot day dim, a bedsheet partition is billowing in the corner, -- Yoficator -- · -- Who are You Addressing, Old Man -- · -- You, «Naderi „of the Caves“», are A Yoficatoreeny And I am Not Standing For It In This Roominghouski Or Anywhere -- frizzling grizzling «Setian» is drawing pungently closer to the group of young men, the twins popping their head out from behind some crates, a delicate spider weightlessly striding across shirting, one of the «the „Arests“» is edging back toward the kitchen portal in the simmering of the confrontation is rolling a halfturn to the side of «Setian»--and stepping away, although maintaining his orientation against his fellows, wincing at the stench--is looking sternly at the two, «Arest the „Hairy“» is slipping away from «Naderi „of the Caves“» entering the kitchen to sit just above Nadia's head on the table is rocking his legs against our sheet partition, -- And You are Leaving Here And You are Giving Your Friendkins The Ghosty For Your Rendezvouses with «Creepity» -- knudging «Arest the „Merkin“» is nodding absently, -- The Fate Of This Letter, This Seems Like Something Pleasing To You Old Man, If You are So Strongly Believing In Order And Ordination, Thoroughness -- · -- Indeed You are Admitting Your Consternation About This Letter Of Which You Should Be Forgetful, Have You No Confidence The ADA is In Possession Of Knowledge In Excess of Yours, With All The Resources At Their Disposal, About The Valuation Of A Single Letterling In The Bloatation Of Our Alphabet, A Redundant Letterlet, Ubiquitous, Yes Perhaps, But Desiring Its Presence is Nothing More Than Romanticization By Reactionary Childrenpoos -- · -- It is Our Cultural Heritage -- · -- It is Simply A Letter Brother, You're Finding It Such A Significant Burdenment is Beyond My Imagination, Its Elision is--Contrarily--Liberatory -- · -- You Sir You are Making The Elisionary Sounds In Your Own Speech, Exclaiming We Don't Need This Very Letter -- silence, -- Impudence, You Willy Nilly, You Silly, I am Verging On Getting The Transportee To «The Mucentle», Oh They Have Significant Interest In These Matters, Don't They «Aresticulus» -- «Arest the „Merkin“» staring at his boots rubbing the cuffs of his pants together and fiddling with the hemline of his blazer, -- Attendance Brother, You Two are Ignorant, You are Desirous Of Listening To This Boy «Setian», I am Not Responsible, I've No Interaction With «Creep», Your Information is Useless -- · -- No Information is Useless Brotherkin -- · -- Attendance Please, I'm Simply In Possession Of Some Yofication Pamphlets -- · -- Aha Kasha, And Where are You Getting These Teensy Pamphlets -- · -- It is Of No Consequence -- · -- No Information is Useless, Especially In A Matter Countering The Providence Of Our Very Berry Lives -- · -- You are Not Living, You Have No Information, You Have Knowledge Of Nothing -- · -- I Have Knowledge Of My Own Devotion, I Have Your Slippery Admission In The Presence Of These Witnesskies, And I Have My Inroad To The Adamin, It is A Case For Them Now, I Have A Belief It is Incredibly Interesting Coming From Little Me -- «Arest the „Merkin“» is moving in for teteatete of vacant contrition with «Naderi „of the Caves“» shoving him away is crumbling into the filthy softness of his corner, creaking on the stairs and housesounds of «Setian» lying down in his cavity directly above us, folks in resettlement shuffling diligently doublechecking the schema of their dwelling superscription against each other and squinting with delineations of the layout of their dwellings in the air with their fingers, the hopefulness of the persistent hair low on my forehead Nadia is plucking out, -- I am Not Fooling Myself, Resurrecting A Corpse is Impossible, Restoration Of This House is Impossible, The Essence Of Its Formation is Persistent But Not Flowing Through My Hands, Each Application Of My Hands is Begetting A New House, A New Spirit, Resurrecting The Corpses Of The Original Laborers is Impossible, The Voices Of Their Rotten Hands Have No Instructions For My Own -- «the „Geezer“» high atop an extension ladder where a flat roof membrane is covering the projection of the bay window is muttering, grimacing with fine lacerations on the thin metacarpal dermis from sharp twigs and grit from asphaltshingles and an errant shard of glass he is throwing gouts of black sludge onto the concrete below, a stratum of intense heat, «Strea» is clipping the airy finery of Nadia's lousy hair down to her scalp as evenly as possible and washing the patchy dome with harsh soap from cottonwood lye, scattering black across the vista indexical distribution of bituminous poultice on the clapboards of the pale roominghouse and inversely with inspection the suspension of cementitious fragmentation therein is prickling with black pores, Nadia and I are gathering my paperwork and accompanying in the totebag a collection of dandelion greens and small mushrooms from the yard for a picnic, passing beneath the ubiquitous extension ladder -- And Copying, That is Palpably Impossible, What Copying is Possible Of Surfaces Whose Outer Dozen Millimeters are Absent, The Entirety Of The Building's Identity Is In That Absence, Our Imposition is Conjectural, If I Have The Ability Of Copying Or Representing What is Absent, is It Better This Decrepitude In Which There is Some Expression Of Vitality, A Mysterious Echoing Of Its Loss With Harmony In The Gentle Contours Of Erosion -- on a slender breeze through the window in the upstairs room harassing «Neidar» from the top of the ladder -- Our Residence Here is Requiring Certain Things Though, Certain Acquiescences To Intervention Against The Natural Ruination, But I am Insouciant About The Unsightliness Of My Efforts, «Better A Crutch Than An Amputation», A Few Daubings Of A Bituminous Poultice Are Countering Every Potency Of Dilapidation, Which I am Allowing Declaritively And Openly, Not Dishonoring The Funeral Offices Of Its Loquacious Decrepitude -- invasive saplings and fiddleheads growing from mudclods on the concrete, somber folks are carrying stones across the plaza to the «Municipal Center» although the queue is nonexistent, very close to the elevator a door is hanging ajar inward allowing an obtuse trapezium of gloss across the vinyl tile floor, statistically insignificant concentrations of tearose and taupe refractions hang in the pale outdoor air, Nadia is clutching my hand in the silence, into the onepoint distance is stretching a sluice of dim and dully crystalline transoms, I am noticing the walls scant between the surplus of doorways are of a grain that is more fine than the perception of the human eye is capable of perceiving, «the Commandant's» room is vibrato, I am perceiving the granular structure of the wall surface, equilibrious limpid clarity--that within daylight, that through water, that only accreting in the especial compression of great distances--the medium of this room, the «Commandant» is standing with the wings of his greatcoat asymptotic--an ogee vault of boilingly abrasive and obscure moss green--pristine yet dull--wool over the cartography of settlement plattings--abstractions of topographic relief in unbroken loops not parallel but avoiding intersections in sage green, cities and townships in natural black inkspills, concentric red circles--with kilometric radii from citycenters and towncenters legible on implicit rays out from their black originations--are wheeling weaving annuli disintegrating into crescent lunes, asymmetrical gibbous lenses, «vesicae piscis», myriad associations of circular triangles, assumptions of triquetrae and attendant «Reuleaux triangles», convex circular polygons of gradual obliquity within intersections of two or more annular families, strange elongations of concave circular polygons within intersections of two or more annular families--on a greatsheet of onionskin pinprickingly lacy and diaphanous--on the broad desksurface with hemlines reaching to the flanking walls -- Abidance -- the «Commandant» is paging deliberately through a dossier his finger on a short paragraph containing no numbers is compelling him to place the needlepoint of a pair of matte steel dividers at a particular intersection of two red circles and whitefingeringly clutching the handle is exploring the implications of the resultant circle with the circumscribing needlepoint--halting at cities or towns along the way and marking them there with an adhesive dart and in an enumerative column next to the particular source paragraph in the dossier--is reviewing another paragraph and determining--through an ADA appropriation of «Sortes Vergilianae»--its cartographic divination with additional darts and annotations, looking up from his industry to Nadia and I -- Where are You Moving -- · -- «Commandant» I'm Not Following -- through one of the doors behind «the Commandant's» table is ajar to an oblique sliver of daylight with black wall silhouette above and below, the viscous air pregnant with propellent from beneath the doors is condensing in thick encyclics up through the vault of the greatcoat -- A Recategorization Of Your Sentence Of Exile To «Minus 12» Is Necessitating A New Municipal District, Receipt Of A Communication On Your Behalf In Moscow is Resulting In Your Being «Nonreporting Exilee» Status Rather Than Your Original Sentencing Status of «Reporting Exilee» -- · -- Who On My Behalf «Commandant» -- · -- Irrelevant -- breathing softly a contrasting dashdash of movement through the argent sliver of sky, gentle slickness on my skin of Nadia is relaxing her constriction of my hand mouthing a word that is not my word, «Bulgakov», each of «the Commandant's» cartographic darts is pulsing throbbing yawning open landscapes and fellowship, -- These Darts are Notations Of Municipalities Commensurate With Your Recategorization -- transfixion on undulation of the red circles where implicit geometries of flight are marshalling radical lines towards concurrence of a single dart in the virtual powercenter of three circles Moscow, Petrograd, Golovlyovo, «Bulgakov» only «Bulgakov» is in the sympathies of ADA hierarchs, -- Although Your Recategorization is To «Nonreporting Exilee» You Do Not Have Approval Nor Chit For Entrance Through Any ADA Tollgate, Have Awareness That These Radii are Fluctuating And Wherever A Tollgate is In Establishment There is Your Geographic Prohibition, Isolation is Necessary For Your Preservation -- intercession from «Bulgakov» is palliating my anxieties about Anna, -- We are Moving To Sannikov -- · -- With Immediacy -- at the edge of the opaque «Municipal Center» shadow the ornate projection of a dull foamy moulding is lapping over the kerb, a passing auto windowfog, Nadia and I in the gutter are picnicking on mushrooms and dandelion greens, acrid bitter vitality in my temples, my tongue exploring the gills, the pumpcar is disembarking, in my jacketpocket clicking I am apportioning the stone carpals with Nadia for sucking--for her triquetrum and hamate, my tongue against the pisiform delicately into the lunate -- Fear is The Gleaming Of Hopefulness --
