rumors of the death of the Daemon--its subduction into the ADA structure--wafting whisperingly between dear friends,

the mollusks are returning to the massive, the evening mist is routinely pleasant and the sky is luminous corpse liver over finely spalling parapets, the fragile neighing of a horse is sounding from the forest just beyond the fencebelt halting the mollusks at their conservative communal foyers, the horse is neighing again and from the city center and crowds from all around the Piazza Basilica are swarming into the vast open crossroads, no horse and autos on the navmesh are halting hissing to the influx and the neighing is emerging from the creaking up portcullis of the great daemonic edifice, the ADA congress is emerging with hesitantly symbiotic footsteps in a rows and columns--unsteadily gazing askance at their flanks for rhythmic concurrence--majestic and haughty with servile mollusks running forth gambolling around the spectacle, the best witchcraft is geometry to the magician's mind--his ordinary acts are feats to devotional mollusks under a deadening platting of silence, we are huddling together in distant amazement--a dull amazement in the buffering of expectancy--where the long procession of human figures with gray skin are marching slowly out of the Basilica, each missing the upper cupola of their craniums--lividity around the orbitals and a timid horizontality to their disposition--where a patching tarpaulin of synthetic material is hirsute with vinyl capillaries terminating at stainless steel serrefine clamps holding cannulae in each raw opening, emitting in their gait a hushingly reverent conspicuousness that from endless supression is falling upon acquiescence, habitual introversion and subjection is dampening our shock of seeing the gray figures streaming forth and turning to dismissive pacification, almost to disdainful humor,

the Daemon emerging, at the end of the queueing phalanx, it is carrying a whip in its trotter, from the broadest circumference of its cranium is emerging--on the basis of geodesics around the triaxial curvature that is passing tangent to the lambdoid suture and the squamous suture and through the frontal bossing--the cantellation of bone into a snubby icosihenagon antiprism of synthetic facets into the 21 triangles and 21 kites of a diminishing trapezohedron converging nearly 1 meter above its gray eyes, a cavernous spire of thought, useless plumage wavering in the whispering ascending from its gray lips into a hailing noise wailing "Intelligence is Improper, I Have The Intelligence! Intelligence is Improper, I Have The Intelligence! Intelligence is Improper, I Have The Most Intelligence!",

a composition of the erect penis of the Daemon emerging from the horn of their uterus are in formaldehyde preservation in an hourglass vitrine atop a porphyry altar in a subcrypt of the Basilica,
