the speckly diffusion of conflicting scrimchannels is bursting forth frothingly from nubile catkins sheathing the streetscape of tracthouse delapidation--the powdery chaff of their dryrotting framing and cladding airborne in invisibly carcinogenic suspension--in crosslaminations over Josef is assisting Nadia lopingly through intestinal involutions--with exceptionally optimal packing density in the preservation of minimum radii necessary for low velocity navmash passage--of vermicular subdivision roadway unfoldingly disgorging into registration with the onepoint perspective of Hinckley Court flattening its culdesac elliptically where a home whose unripe plum front door is residing at the vanishingpoint of doomgrip dollyzoom attraction, zido & zolly & transtrav & contrazoom & pushpull & vertigozoom across the asphaltic whiteout balding is not cracking bleachingly and a wall of invasive evergreens--its bosky depths are fostering glial microenvironments of <<beefwood>> & <<she oak>>--is lacing the sky behind the beige ranchhouse beige on taupe on dollskin on mauvebleach cropping the grayishgreen coniferous branchlets of enarthrodial and furrowingly hairy slenderness of 10 to 20 cm minutely ridging lengths and tiny needly scales around the crotches of branchlets--with quantities of 6 to 8 in Casuarina equisetifolia whorls & quantities of 8 to 10 in Casuarina cunninghamiana whorls & quantities of 10 to 14 in Casuarina glauca whorls--with monoecious inconspicuous femaleness--female plants are a rarity in 11.19--in small axillary clusters & maleness in small terminal spicules bearing tiny monospermous micropterous nutlets--the <<samara>>--ejaculatingly from formations of woody conical clusterings are drifting on the damp breeze to the dampness of Nadia's greengray skin sheen in the white brightness and the sweaty matting of her coiffure is fluffy with cottkins, a garden of dirt & mud patchy with nettles below the steel tube of a chainlink horizonline with gates--numerals scrollsawingly inept and spraypaintingly insitu golden castoff spatterings & slumping pointblank menisci running igneous drying dullness of false gold--interruptingly at 3.7 m oncenter around the liminexurbanization subdivision homeplat of <<Judas Payrite>>--nominally <<Little Judas>> & <<the „Bloodsucker“>> & <<the „Asskisser“>> & <<the „Golden Ass“>> & <<the „Cheez Fonzie“>> & <<Sir Spraycheese>> & <<Judas Playfight>> & <<Ickybod Plain>> & <<PeeRight>> & <<Sir Syr>> & <<Daemonseed>>--around the homeplace of Payrite they are reorienting slightly into the precisely central depression of the culdesac is a drainbody to the stormsewer throwing the home offcenter into more flattering a threequarter perspective for consideration by Josef--Nadia glazing over stumbling--of the beige drainbody of their fates is drawing them down into the earth with exceptional gravitation, selecting one gate in the perimeter fencing with a pathway is leading to the the front door is shutup and the creaking of Josef's weight alighting the silver roughage of plank stairs is shifting the balance of the house framing and Nadia is falling onto the small landing shaking the house and the door is falling open, the fetid breath of utilitarian cookery upon loosenings of wood particulate -- I'm Falling -- the authentic ugliness of gold in pus distillation is the sickness of every surface of dermis & hairshaft, the most effective rendering qualitatively is the greenness of illness or rottenness with flashing pus white specularity with just a golden--the virtual aura of gold occupying the cultural consciousness--corona, every surface is a funeral parlor, every surface is reeking, every surface is emblematic of the thinness of goldplating, goldplating is chipping away from particlewood gildingly superficially, foreground and background are blackness with a micron of goldweave molecular thin lattice over umbral motion is scuttling and furrowing through a stria of iceblue glowing across the dark hallway wall and ceiling in the dusty silence gingerly coaxing the door to the ikon room--of lightest particlewood whispering not heavily enough for squeaking hinges--floating into the room where Daemonic holikons--in pyramids of luminosity at the vertex of floor two walls of the brownstudy--the wall is the pictureplane is Igrat V Testo's cave and its relationship with perceiving reality upsidedown and backwards in the occupation of quotidian rooms embodying the masslike rabble of molluscs with spacelike projections on the walls of the spaces of occupation are the monotony of placing a luminous figuration on the wall that isn't lying on the same plane as the wall--slightly in front of it or is seemingly making a hole through it--illustrative of the plasticity and malleability of the luminous medium into a gelatinous malignancy of tangible fog to touch, illumination of hypnagogic lucidity--intense hues radiating off facets and fauna for the definition of the space in lieu of tangible masses manifesting the space--at the fringes of perception, the hue cadaverously cerulean--the lucid manifestation of an aloof Daemon -- My Dearest Darlingy The Daemon -- whispering to rattling stylus fingertips on linoleum on concrete on granite on glass are gesturing silently inputting data into the platter--Payrite is kneeling--shifting his eyes to the corner of the holicon of <<the ADA „Kakokrator“>> is a vacant luminous pyramid testpattern--with an enigmatic mixture of filial reverence and venomous coveting that he--only a man--is daydreamingly usurping an entire vaporous bureaucracy with a schema of operations in translation from his outwitting of a neighbor man into giving him a swath of yard for the erection of a fence that is blocking out the cloudlight from his nettles, kneeling before the fastidious ikon so quietly and modestly and so intently indulging this puissant fantasy that teardrops are welling in his wide eyes awaiting the <<appearance>> of the <<Kakokrator>>, in the hallway at the top of the half staircase running to the upper half of the house a golden head is floating on a square white chargerplate drooping everywhere is darkness is blackness & sootiness upon the airy powder of coaldust vaporization dim, welling up glassiness of the staring eyes and the mouth hanging limply above a crimson neck and the golden wicker of his hair is--with the assistance of a slender and elegant coryphee holding the head aloft on its platter in drapery of predominant vermilion emberingly ardent incandescent viscose goldwarping with resinous smearings of mustard olibanum & olivine damask gaseous across the fabric trailing through violet gas plumage of azurite flambe with limpid carbuncle & emerald wormrot fringiness is lofting and stagnantly billowing furrily in its tumbling down the risers smearing drybrush strands of souse and headcheese hue assortments are zoetropic through slender balusters iridescent with condensation of distinctive azure luminance spanning to the handrail with patchings and reinforcements in argent cement and aureate hotglue--descending the staircase toward the equimolecular blooddrench of aniline & toluidine and atrabilious gorewipe varnishing of the ensiform newelpost, any photons are reverberant photons coming into the house on the surface of the outerwear & shoes and launched toward a color then back weakly to the retina, and all the attendant bouncing the imprisonment of all stowaway photons lurking and languishing in the desolation of the house, clicking long fingernails resonant into the flesh of the fingertips are clicking down the black throat of the hallway on the upper storey of the house in a meditative cadence underlying the shuffling forth of footsteps from the dark, the walls of the stairwell black with the inheritence of glowing indigo though no receipt of directional illumination a golden head golden skin and golden hair is floating down the staircase upon the charger of a broad white puritan collar is draping over virtual crossbar of black shoulders--, the distantly peaceful gaze of preoccupation--the tabulation of the vista--laying a snaretrap for a victim, chromakey compositing him into the darkness of the wallpaper though vaguely--as the eyes are adjusting--legible against the hairline arabesque inscriptions on wallpaper of lapis lozenges and nacreous marquetry with the glimmerings of prismatic flaming spectra, the corporeal foreground of which is becoming apparent in the ponderous shadowy robe & rational pantaloons in black serge with twill of bronze weft where he is stopping halfway down the stairs, the golden paste excretion from the the drooping platter of the puritan partlet--in lustrous mercerization of cotton--slouching and upon halting partway down the stairs is erecting the horribly ascending head upon the gory chasuble torrent arterioles and blood unstanchably is gushing forth of gore and dripping from anenome of nerves ghastly glass eyes and he dreaming his location amongst the Daemone is intoning -- That Supping isn't Just The Wallpaper My Darlings--Although it's Pervyy And Soaking Up All Of Our Breath--The Aroma In The Air--It's Luxurious--You are Smelling The Fresh Cabbage Soup With The Reclaimation Of Broth--Conservation In The Kitchen is Benevolence To The Basilica--Regardless It is The Most Delicious Broth, The Saltiness is In Perfect Equilibrium, This House is Full Of The Most Delectable Food, Saline Goose And Ray Cutlets, Roasty Ewe Mutton And Woodpigeon, And A Pudding Of Creamy Raspberry pie, Josef Your Mouth is Dropping Open, If You are Perceptive Through The Lunch Of Liver & Mushrooms In Sourcream & Custardcake, The Kitchen is Not Accessible To You, Perhaps, No, But A Domecile Isn't Prescriptive, The Guidelines are Fluxuating, The Kitchen is Upstairs, The Neighbors are Telling The Daemon, They are Whispering But it's Audible For Me, I am Hearing All The Secret Things, Their Whispering is Audible, They are Calling Me <<Pyrite>>, It's Complimentary, I'm Shimmering, My Hearing is Too Exceptional And It is Troubling Me With All Of This Overwhelming Information I am Sorting Through And Filing And Determining What The Daemone are Desirous Of, The Neighbors are Whispering To Their Holikons <<Oh, I am saving so much food for the hoppers>>, <<Oh, my devotion is starving me to death>>, It is The Big Untruth, Their Exasperation is In Forsaking So Much But They are Standing In The Shadiness Of Their Gardens Eating Cake, Nobody is Talking About It But Me, I've An Adoration For Starvation, I am The Only One Saying This, But I am Eating Happily And So Luxuriously, My Dearest Friend Josef, You're Thinking That I am Chucking You A Piece With The Subsidization Of Your Habitation Here, I've So Many Chuckable Pieces, It's A Verifiable Fact, I am Quite Comfortable, You Needn't With This Selfconsciousness Animating Your Visage, I'm Only In Receipt Of 0,78ƫ For Each Of Your Precious Heads, And That is Truly Beautiful, My Benevolence is In No Relation To The Recompense But For The Powerful--And Wholly Personal And Undetectably Interior--Sentiments Of Generosity, I've Sent Three Dozen Neighbors To The White Sea Coast Where They're Building The Dikes, The Earthworks, The Levees, And I'm Only In Receipt Of 3,56ƫ From The ADA For Each Conscription, It is Outstanding, I am Not Denigrating That Recompense, is That The Worth Of Human Soul, It is Not My Determination, The Daemone are Knowledgeable, The People In This Neighborhood are Idiotic, My Adoration For Them is Boundless, These Idiots are Saying <<Payrite where am I most productive in servicework to the ADA>> And They are Signing My Name To Their Conscription Papers And I've No Certainty But Certainly They are Dying For The Benevolent Fortitude Of The ADA In These Earthworks On The Coast, And Their Landplats And Their Belongings are Mine Of Course, I've No Need For Them, I've Too Much, Their Idiotic Things, I've No Requirement Of Them, You are Seeing That I am Desirous Of Nice Things, Possessions Shimmeringly Wafting Through The Stillness are Alive On Their Own, I'm Not Calling This Existence <<Encrustation>> But I've Awareness That It is Of Swaddlingliness, I've No Need For Every Thing, The Median Area Of Plats In This Court is 1.85 Decares While This Plat being A Radial Segment On The Culdesac is 2 Decares And Additionaly It is Abutting The Forest Which is Essentially In My Possession As Well, I'm In Possession Of The Conscriptees Properties And I'm Not Using Them, I've No Purpose For Them, Not That I've All Of Them, Am I Wanting Them All, Yes, I've This Feeling Of Sprawlingly, You Must've Awareness Of How Much I'm Desirous Of An Adventure On The Coast, My Conscriptees are Returning From Coastal Duties With New Skillsets, They are Preparing Sweettreats, Experts In Butchery--My Man <<Isetan>> On Nancy Davis Lane is Killing The Beasts Himself In His Basement--A Gardemanger In Allover Seagreen Mosaic Whose Construction I've Responsibility For--And Making All Sorts Of Wonderful Charcuterie Bliss--Sausage & Drob & Mousseline & Pâté & Galyntyne & Confit & Feet Of All Ilks & Organmeat--Kidneys & Sweetbreads & Liver & Brainstem For Soup & Gizzards & Snacking Eyes & Testicles-- & Saucisson & Lucanica & Kiełbasa Biała & Luxurious Black Mustamakkara & Amourette & Headcheese & Creier Pane--I am Salivating, They are Gaining Skills In Holography, Trenching, Haberdashery, The General Fine Art Of Servitude--Fancy Meal Preparation, Proper Dinner Service--<<Service À La Russe>>--, Scullery Duties, Nursing, Custodial Finesse--, As Well As Craftiness At Gilding, At Goldwork Embroidery--Expert Utilization Of Golden Torsade & Lizerine & Purl For Maximization Of Golden Surfacearea in Damask--, Right Here With Us On Hinckley Court is A Man So Skillful In Carpentry And Woodturning He is Deeply Thankful For His Conscription <<Payrite, my gratitude is without depth>> And I've The Belief He is Genuine About That, What A Miraculous Experiential Repertoire--Learning Consumption Of Seal Liver In The Encampments The Vertices Of His Lips are Cracking Back Through His Cheeks, Falling Asleep In The Trench, Mistaking This For Death His Mates are Burying Him--, I am Envious, Photography Of The Shoreline is Breathtaking, The Sun--The Sun--is Glimmering Across The Wavelets In The Wideopen Water--, The Uninterruption Of My Presence Here is A Requirement However, Servitude is A Sedimentary Institution, Children, And Although Those On The Outer Layers are Treading Upon It is I Deeper Within The Matrix Who is In Banishment From The Sunlight, Here is My Interment, Suffixes, Prefixes, Diminutives Atop Diminutives, Jargon, It's All Baggage, You're Bringing So Little Into This House With You, You've So Little In This World, How are You Existing, What are You Accounting For, What are You Tabulating, You are Tabulating The Things That are Belonging To Other People, And You are Dying And These Other People are Living Forever, Possessions aren't Nominally <<Possessions>> Because Of Your Ownership Of Them But Because You are Possessing Them, Your Spirit is Inside Them Possessing Them, I am Only Desirous Of Integuments, This is All That is Available To The Sensations, The Concrete Monstrosity--The Solid Emptiness--Beside The Parkway On That Disrepairious Swardlet is Not In My Possession, I'm Not Desirous Of It, It is A Mystery, The Municipal Documentation is Byzantine--The Schematic Constellation Of It All is In My Visual Consciousness, I'm Seeing The Turgid Diffusion Of Its Ownership In The Concealment Of Layers And Layers Of Shells With Little Strandlets Of Artifacts Of Transactions All With The Prerogative Of Erasing Its Ownership--But Fortunately It is Not Of Importance To Me And How is A Plat Of Property Without An Owner Beneficial To Municipal Orderliness, Who is Controlling Its Perimeter And Who is Providing Guidance About Pedestrian access and routing, The ADA is The Only Entity With The Sensibility For The Determination Of Desirelines, The Sward is Simply A Mudpit Without An Agent Of The ADA, There is No Fence And The Worst Kind Of People are Just Streaming Across It, They are Possibly Nice People, I've No Certainty Of It, The Whole Uncertainty Of It is Soluable With A Series Of Gates And Quotidian Pathways, It is My Determination That Railings Or Guardwalls are Not Necessary Beside The Pathway, The Inscription Of A Pathway is An Effective Enough Countermeasure Especially In Conjunction With Gates At Its Termini, I've Gates All Around <<Payriteskip>>, You've Only Accessibility To The Back Door Of This House Downstairs And The Quotidian Path In Connection With It, You've Not Permission For Front Door Usage, The Front Door is Leading To The Upstairs And My Chambers--With The Inclusion Of The Kitchen--And To The Twins' Chambers, For All Of Your Consideration This Home is A Massive, It is The Concrete Megalith By The Parkway Albeit On The Culdesac And A Construction Of Wood And Fiberboard, Your Consciousness is Your Own And You are Thinking What are Thinking, Your Consciousness is Singing <<A Youthful Cock, A Youthful Cock, His Claw Sawsharp, He's Threatening The Hen, „Koo Koo Roo Koo Koo Roo“, The Hen is Crying, „Clucky Clucky Koo Koo“, But Crying Crying Through Her Bloody Bloody Boo Boo>>, You are Saying What You are Saying Whispering To Each Other But You are Abiding By The Guidelines, I'm Walking Out Into The Snow And Lying Down For The Greatly Peaceful Slumbering And You are Not Ascending These Stairs, You are Not Seeing The Twins, You Cannot, By The Guidelines It is Not A Possibility, The Most Opportune Gate For Your Ingression is 10.14 On The Rear, Accessible Only Through The Forest, The Twins are Here In The Swaddling Of My Hospitibleness, it's Not A Necessity For Me, I've No Necessity For The 0,78ƫ Each, it's Not A Necessity For Me, However Rebuffing The Compensation is An Affront To The Daemon And It is Desireable For The Sole Dedication Of The <<Community Reclaimation Financials>>, It is A Perfectly Laudable Application Of The Funding, I am Not Dedicating The Money For Praiseworthiness, It is Laudable Nonetheless, It is For The Greater Benefit Of The Daemon, The ADA Has Knowledge Of This I am Certain, Look At Mee, I'm The Concealment Of Nothing, I am All Obedience And Devotion, Not Only For Fear But Out Of Duty To You Brother Josef, And You are Joining The Twins In This Service To The Community, What Else, No Animals, No Animals, And The Daemon is Thankful For Your Compliance With The Guidelines -- in his benevolent oration his eyes are setting a snaretrap, -- Sir All I am Truly Desirous Of is A Bed For My Wife, She is Very Ill -- with commentary in suspension on the stagnant air--seemingly in the midst of a continuation of his introduction--he is floating back to the top of the staircase back disappearing into the dim into the distant voices of women hushing and doors closingly hushing, the glib fetus Payrite is scrutinizing the surroundings of the room from the glistening of bilious afterbirth in the otherwise empty beige antimicrobial bedstead amassing the bedclothes for himself in protection from nobody and is thanking the empty room profusely, resistance is impossible against the appearance of such devotion, resistance is impossible against the desirousness of passing him the finest piece of food on the plate,


